Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology Alumni Association records, [ca. 1928-2010].
New York State College of Human Ecology Alumni Association records
- HEAA 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Part I
    - Board of Directors term ends
    - Committee Chairs
    - Goals & Objectives
    - Mission Statement & Long Range Plan
    - Minutes
      - Executive Committee Meeting, June 5, 1992
      - New Board Member Orientation, June 5, 1992
      - Board of Directors, June 5, 1992
      - Annual Meeting, June 6, 1992
      - Executive Committee Conference Call, July 21, 1992
      - Board of Directors, October 10, 1992
      - Executive Committee, January 29, 1993
      - Board of Directors, January 30, 1992
      - Board of Directors, April 24, 1993
    - Notes Break-out Session, April 24, 1993
    - Policy of Financial Affairs, May 1993
    - Projected Budget, 1992-1993
    - Treasurer's Report, August 31, 1992
    - Asset Statement, October 8, 1992
    - Investment Account/Endowment Fund, August 31, 1992
    - Operating Fund/Asset Statement, January 27, 1993
    - Investment Account/Endowment Fund, January 26, 1993
    - Operating Fund, April 20, 1993
    - Asset Statement, April 20, 1993
    - Investments/Life Membership Endowment, April 20, 1993
    - Operating Fund/Asset Statement, May 31, 1993
    - Investments/Life Membership Endowment, August 31, 1993
    - Operating Fund Final, 1992-1993
  - Part II - Committee Reports
    - Student Representatives, August 5, 1992
    - Student Activities - Grant Loans, December 16, 1992
    - Student Activities - Grant Loans, June 10, 1993
    - History & Archives, January 27, 1993
    - Nominations & Elections, March 12, 1993
    - Honors & Recognition, January 30, 1993
    - Membership, July 10, 1992
    - Public Relations, January 19, 1993
    - Annual & Special Events, September 14, 1992
    - Annual & Special Events, December 28, 1992
    - Financial
      - Policy on Financial Matters, January 28, 1993
      - Expense Approval Procedure, January 26, 1993
      - Dues Deposit Procedure, January 26, 1993
      - Checking Account Procedure, January 26, 1993
    - Grants & Loan Policy, March 25, 1993
    - Grants & Loan Policy, January 26, 1993
    - Loan Repayment Agreement, January 27, 1993
    - Process for Development of Alumni Association
      - Plan of Work & Budget
  - Part III
    - Miscellaneous & Supporting Information
    - Committee Work Plan, 1992-1993
      - Annual & Special Events
      - Development
      - History & Archives
      - Honors & Recognition
      - Long Range
      - Membership
      - Nominations & Elections
      - Public Relations
      - Student Activities - Grants & Loans
      - Student Recruitment
    - Invitations
      - Honoring Founders of our College, September 1, 1992
      - Homecoming, October 23-24, 1992
      - Senior Reception, April 23, 1993
    - Human Ecology Reunion Events
    - Alumni Breakfast & 66th Annual Meeting, June 6, 1993
    - Call to Meeting, June 5-6, 1992
    - Agenda, June 5, 1992
    - Call to Meeting, October 9-10, 1992
    - Agenda, October 10, 1992
    - Call to Meeting, January 29-30, 1993
    - Agenda, January 29-30, 1993
    - Call to Meeting, January 24, 1993
    - Agenda, January 24, 1993
    - Weekend Schedule Leadership Weekend, April 22-24, 1993
    - The Reappointment of Francille Firebaugh: The View of Faculty - E. Scott Maynes, January 29, 1993
    - Alumni in Action Jeffrey L. Olson '76
  - Part IV
    - Presidents, 1926-
    - Distinguished Teaching Award, 1979-
    - Helen Bull Vandervort Achievement Award, 1983-
    - Dean's Award when given
- HEAA 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Part I
    - Picture Board, Winter 1993
    - Board of Directors Booklet
    - Committee Chairs
    - Committee Membership
    - Minutes
      - Board of Directors, June 11, 1993
      - Annual Meeting, June 12, 1993
      - Conference Call, June 22, 1993
      - Board of Directors, November 6, 1993
      - Resolution: Investment Policy (original and revised)
      - Draft: A Challenge Program in support of teh Campaign, October 13, 1993
      - Board of Directors, January 21, 1994
    - Budget 1993-94 Adopted, November 6, 1993
    - Operating Fund, august 31, 1993
      - Assets statement, August 31, 1993
      - Investments/Life Membership Endowment, November 5, 1993
    - Operating Fund
      - Assets statement, January 18, 1994
      - Investments/Life Membership Endowment, January 18, 1994
    - Operating Fund, June 8, 1994
      - Assets statement, June 8, 1994
      - Investments/Life Membership Endowment, June 8, 1994
    - Operating Fund, August 31, 1994
    - HEAA Membership Dues Deposits, 1994
  - Part II
    - Committee Reports
      - 1993 Membership Drive, June 9, 1993
      - 1993 Membership Drive, August 31, 1993
      - 1994 Membership Drive, January 18, 1993
    - Strategy for Campaign to raise $30000, June 10, 1994
    - Developmental/Challenge Fund
      - Letter to Alumni
      - Priority Endowment Needs of the College
    - Student Activities, May 27, 1994
    - History Archives, June 20, 1994
    - Index of Institutes, 1952-1978
    - Finance Committee Annual Report, June 29, 1994
      - Policies on Financial Affairs
      - Investment Policy
    - Display Case MVR Hall, December 20, 1993
      - Schedule, December 15, 1993
    - Report from the Alumni Relations Office, June 10, 1994
  - Part III
    - Booklet Alumni Breakfast - 67th Annual Meeting, June 12, 1993
    - HE Reunion Events, June 12, 1993
      - Letters from Brenda Bricker to HEAA Board - A Proposal for Alumni Support from Bernice Hopkins sharing info on an alum Ruth Davis '17 on her 100th birthday, June 17, 1994
      - Call to Meeting, June 11, 1993
      - Agenda, November 6, 1993
      - ----Missing Agenda, January 21, 1994
      - Invitation for "Alumni Career Talk", November 6, 1993
      - Senior Reception
      - Sam Beck Cornell Field Study Program
      - Extern Sponsors, 1993
  - Part IV
    - Historical Perspective
    - Presidents, 1926-
    - Distinguished Teaching Award, 1979-
    - Helen Bull Vandervont Achievement Award, 1983-
- HEAA 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Part I
    - Board of Directors - Booklets and Lists
    - Committee Chairs
    - Minutes
      - Board of Directors, June 10, 1994
      - Addendum (Date of incorporation), March 21, 1994
      - Annual Meeting, June 11, 1994
      - Board Meeting, September 17, 1994
      - Board Meeting, January 27, 1995
      - Proposal Budget, 1994-1995
      - Revised Budget, 1994-1995
      - Letter from Treasurer Oakleaf to Board, March 13, 1994
      - Operating Fund Final 1993-94, August 31, 1994
        - Assets, August 31, 1994
        - Investments/Life Membership Endowment, September 12, 1994
      - Operating Fund Final 1993-94, September 1, 1994
        - Investment Funds income, January 24, 1995
        - Assets, January 25, 1995
      - Operating Fund Final 1994-95, August 31, 1995
        - Investment Funds income, June 9, 1995
        - Assets, June 9, 1995
  - Part II
    - Committee Reports (also in minutes)
    - Ad Hoc - Bylaws revision
    - Annual and Special Events Committee
    - Finance
    - History and Archives report
    - Honors and Recognition
    - Membership total, August 31, 1994
    - Membership total, January 20, 1995
    - Membership total, June 6, 1995
    - History of Dues and Membership Totals
    - Work Plan, 1994-1995
    - Nominations and Elections
    - Scholarship Challenge Committee
    - Undergraduate Scholarship Fund, January 18, 1995
    - List of Fund supporters, June 4, 1995
      - Student Activities
        - Copy of Student Societies: The Interchange, April 1995
        - Alumni Speaker, 1994
        - Grants and Loans, 1994-1995
      - Student Recruitment
      - Campaign Report, September 17, 1994
      - Report from alumni relations office HEAA, June 10, 1994
  - Part III
    - Call to Meeting, June 10, 1994
    - Call to Meeting, September 17, 1994
    - Call to Meeting, January 27, 1994
    - Alumni Career Talk, September 16, 1994
    - Senior Reception Invitation, May 4, 1995
    - 25 Years as Human Ecology, June 1995
    - "How Does Your Diet Measure Up?"
    - "Raising Children in a Toxic Environment"
    - Donor Recognition
    - Rediliction Ceremony of Portraits of College Founders Invitation
    - 68th Annual Meeting and Alumni Breakfast Program
    - Bulletin from Helen Bull Vandervort Memorial Service, August 8, 1994
    - Crossdressing: exchange of clothing styles among cultures- closing celebration invitation, August 19, 1994
  - Part IV
    - Historical Perspective
    - Presidents, 1926-
    - Distinguished Teaching Award, 1979-
    - Helen Bull Vandervort Achievement Award, 1983-
    - Deans Award When Given
- HEAA 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Part I
    - Board of Directors Booklet and Items (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Board of Directors, September 23, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Board of Directors, January 26, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Board of Directors, June 7, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - College Campaign Report, June 9, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Board meeting- Agenda, June 8-9, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Alumni Association Bylaws, June 10, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Board of Directors, January 26, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Reunion Breakfast, September 23, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Board of Directors, June 7-8, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Class Biographies, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Class Biographies, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Class Biographies, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Class Biographies, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Class Biographies, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Class Biographies, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Class Biographies, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Various Committee Records, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Various Committee Records, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Various Committee Records, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Various Committee Records, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 23-24)
- Various Committee Records, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 25-26)
- Various Committee Records, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Finance Committee Records, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Various Committee Records, 2000-2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Board of Directors Meeting, September 2006 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Board of Directors Meeting, June 2006 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Board of Directors Meeting, January 2007 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Board of Directors Meeting, May 2007 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Board of Directors Meeting, October 2007 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Board of Directors Meeting, January 2008 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Board of Directors Meeting, April 2008 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Board of Directors Meeting, September 2008 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Board of Directors Meeting, February 2009 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Board of Directors Meeting, April 2009 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Board of Directors Meeting, October 2009 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Board of Directors Meeting, January 2010 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Board of Directors Meeting, April 2010 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- History of HEAA, Up to 1996 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Focus Group Research, January 2003 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Helen Bull Vandervort Award, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
- Alumnus Recipient List, 1999-2003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Cornell Club Speakers, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Membership History, 1997-2006 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- HEAA Handbooks, 1997, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- HEAA Faculty Speakers, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- William White - San Antonio, Texas, April 2006 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Helene Dillard - Auburn, March 2006 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Sean Nicholson - Albany, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Don Tobias - New York City, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Richard Burkhauser - Connecticut, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Susan Ashdown - Boston, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Kay Obendorf - California, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Richard Burkhauser - Westchester, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- HEAA Certificate of Corporation, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- HEAA Leadership Initiative, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Human Ecology Ambassador Handbook, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Memos, Event Brochures and Invitations, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- By-Laws, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- HEAA Board Meetings, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 21-22)
- HEAA Board Meetings, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- HEAA Board Meetings, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- HEAA Board Meetings, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- HEAA Board Meetings, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Event Brochures and Invitations, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- HEAA Board Meetings, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Event Brochures and Invitations, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- HEAA Board Meetings, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- HEAA Board Meetings, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- HEAA Board Meetings, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- HEAA Board Meetings, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- HEAA Board Meetings, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- HEAA Board Meetings, January 2011 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Reunion Breakfast Programs, 2001, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Board of Directors Booklets, 1997-1999-2005-2006 (Box 5)